You can lose the match away from the
pool table. What do I mean by that?
Well, we all know these players that are
shouting from the rooftops, I do
everything for my sport. Well, are you
really? How about your diet? Junk food
or healthy food? Are you working out?
Couch potato or healthy and fit? What
are you watching? Dogs on skateboards or
actually studying matches? How about
your focus? Do you have a daily routine
for training your mind like meditation
or visualization or zero? What about
your sleep? Are you reaching the
recommended 7 to n hours a night or are
you way under and really low on energy
and screen time? Are you limiting
yourself and having strong focus and
presence or are you dumping all your
mental energy and watching other
people's lives? You see, you can
practice all you want, but if this
framework is lacking, you're going to
have trouble reaching your full
potential. So start making small changes
in these departments and bring out the
best of yourself